http://www.war-toys.com/privacy-policy.aspx

items in my cart: 0
current subtotal: $0.00
view cart | checkout
"Taking War To A Whole New Scale..."
** Clearance **** Custom **** NEW **** PRE-ORDER **1/12 Scale3RACE WorkshopAlert LineBlue BoxCal-TekCastle CollectiblesCyber HobbyDAM!!DragonDragon In DreamsE & SFacepoolFlagsetGameitoyGear Of The Unkown : G.O.T.U. GEARHobby MasterHuman WaveIn The Past ToysIQOKADHOBBYKGB Hobby StudioKing's ToysMajor DesignMax ToysMILMini TimesOther CompaniesRedmanRoyal BestSideshow CollectiblesSoldier CountrySoldier StoryToys CityTwisting ToyzUjindouVortoysWar StoryYellow Submarine
<a href="#" onclick="window.open(" https:="" seals.networksolutions.com="" siteseal_seek="" siteseal?v_shortname="NETSP&amp;v_querytype=W&amp;v_search=www.war-toys.com&amp;x=5&amp;y=5" ,"netsp","width="450,height=500,toolbar=no,location=no,directories=no,status=no,menubar=no,scrollbars=no,copyhistory=no,resizable=no");return"" false;"="">
<a href="#" onclick="window.open(" https:="" seals.networksolutions.com="" siteseal_seek="" siteseal?v_shortname="NETSP&amp;v_querytype=W&amp;v_search=www.war-toys.com&amp;x=5&amp;y=5" ,"netsp","width="450,height=500,toolbar=no,location=no,directories=no,status=no,menubar=no,scrollbars=no,copyhistory=no,resizable=no" );return""="" false;"="">
Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Information we collect
When ordering or registering, your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. maybe required.
What we use your information for
Site Improvement
Improve Service
Transaction Speed
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Do we disclose information to outside parties?
War-Toys does  not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally information.
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on January 31, 2009.
Questions and feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.
Online Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE. All users of this site agree that access to and use of this site are subject to the following terms and conditions and other applicable law. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this site.
Copyright
The entire content included in this site, including but not limited to text, graphics or code is copyrighted as a collective work under the United States and other copyright laws, and is the property of War-Toys. The collective work includes works that are licensed to War-Toys. Copyright 2003, War-Toys ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Permission is granted to electronically copy and print hard copy portions of this site for the sole purpose of placing an order with War-Toys or purchasing War-Toys products. You may display and, subject to any expressly stated restrictions or limitations relating to specific material, download or print portions of the material from the different areas of the site solely for your own non-commercial use, or to place an order with War-Toys or to purchase War-Toys products. Any other use, including but not limited to the reproduction, distribution, display or transmission of the content of this site is strictly prohibited, unless authorized by War-Toys. You further agree not to change or delete any proprietary notices from materials downloaded from the site.
Trademarks
All trademarks, service marks and trade names of War-Toys used in the site are trademarks or registered trademarks of War-Toys
Warranty Disclaimer
This site and the materials and products on this site are provided "as is" and without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied. To the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, War-Toys disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. War-Toys does not represent or warrant that the functions contained in the site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that the defects will be corrected, or that this site or the server that makes the site available are free of viruses or other harmful components. War-Toys does not make any warrantees or representations regarding the use of the materials in this site in terms of their correctness, accuracy, adequacy, usefulness, timeliness, reliability or otherwise. Some states do not permit limitations or exclusions on warranties, so the above limitations may not apply to you.
Limitation of Liability
War-Toys shall not be liable for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the materials on this site or the performance of the products, even if War-Toys has been advised of the possibility of such damages. Applicable law may not allow the limitation of exclusion of liability or incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.
Typographical Errors
In the event that a War-Toys product is mistakenly listed at an incorrect price, War-Toys reserves the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for product listed at the incorrect price. War-Toys reserves the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is cancelled, War-Toys shall issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the incorrect price.
Term; Termination
These terms and conditions are applicable to you upon your accessing the site and/or completing the registration or shopping process. These terms and conditions, or any part of them, may be terminated by War-Toys without notice at any time, for any reason. The provisions relating to Copyrights, Trademark, Disclaimer, Limitation of Liability, Indemnification and Miscellaneous, shall survive any termination.
Notice
War-Toys may deliver notice to you by means of e-mail, a general notice on the site, or by other reliable method to the address you have provided to War-Toys.
Miscellaneous
Your use of this site shall be governed in all respects by the laws of the state of California, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law provisions, and not by the 1980 U.N. Convention on contracts for the international sale of goods. You agree that jurisdiction over and venue in any legal proceeding directly or indirectly arising out of or relating to this site (including but not limited to the purchase of War-Toys products) shall be in the state or federal courts located in Los Angeles County, California. Any cause of action or claim you may have with respect to the site (including but not limited to the purchase of War-Toys products) must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. War-Toys's failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of these terms and conditions shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Neither the course of conduct between the parties nor trade practice shall act to modify any of these terms and conditions. War-Toys may assign its rights and duties under this Agreement to any party at any time without notice to you.
Use of Site
Harassment in any manner or form on the site, including via e-mail, chat, or by use of obscene or abusive language, is strictly forbidden. Impersonation of others, including a War-Toys or other licensed employee, host, or representative, as well as other members or visitors on the site is prohibited. You may not upload to, distribute, or otherwise publish through the site any content which is libelous, defamatory, obscene, threatening, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, abusive, illegal, or otherwise objectionable which may constitute or encourage a criminal offense, violate the rights of any party or which may otherwise give rise to liability or violate any law. You may not upload commercial content on the site or use the site to solicit others to join or become members of any other commercial online service or other organization.
Participation Disclaimer
War-Toys does not and cannot review all communications and materials posted to or created by users accessing the site, and is not in any manner responsible for the content of these communications and materials. You acknowledge that by providing you with the ability to view and distribute user-generated content on the site, War-Toys is merely acting as a passive conduit for such distribution and is not undertaking any obligation or liability relating to any contents or activities on the site. However, War-Toys reserves the right to block or remove communications or materials that it determines to be (a) abusive, defamatory, or obscene, (b) fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading, (c) in violation of a copyright, trademark or; other intellectual property right of another or (d) offensive or otherwise unacceptable to War-Toys in its sole discretion.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless War-Toys, its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers (collectively the "Service Providers") from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees, resulting from any violation of these terms and conditions or any activity related to your account (including negligent or wrongful conduct) by you or any other person accessing the site using your Internet account.
Third-Party Links
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, War-Toys may link to sites operated by third parties. However, even if the third party is affiliated with War-Toys, War-Toys has no control over these linked sites, all of which have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of War-Toys. These linked sites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, War-Toys seeks to protect the integrity of its web site and the links placed upon it and therefore requests any feedback on not only its own site, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work).
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Email Address:
Password:
Remember Me
Create an account
Forgot Password?
Email Address:
Home | About Us | Contact Us | My Account | Shipping Policy | Return Policy | Privacy Policy | Pricing Policy | Payment Methods | Sitemap | Cart Help
We Gladly Accept The Following Forms Of Payment:
DISCLAIMER: These Are Collector Items Intended For Ages 15+ | CHOKING HAZARD: Some Products May Contain Small Parts Not Intended For Children Under 5 Years
© 2020War-Toys
